//Array of Question Objects
const trivia = [
  {
    prompt: "What is Beyoncé's middle name?",
    optA:"CELESTINE",
    optB:"GISELLE",
    optC:"SOLANGE",
    optD:"DESIREE",
    answer: "GISELLE"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Beyoncé rose to fame in the late 1990s as the lead singer of what R&B girl-group?",
    optA:"TLC",
    optB:"DESTINY'S CHILD",
    optC:"EN VOGUE",
    optD:"THE SPICE GIRLS",
    answer: "DESTINY'S CHILD"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Beyoncé made her big screen debut in what movie?",
    optA:"THE PINK PANTHER",
    optB:"ZOOLANDER",
    optC:"DREAMGIRLS",
    optD:"AUSTIN POWERS IN GOLDMEMBER",
    answer: "AUSTIN POWERS IN GOLDMEMBER"
  },
  {
    prompt: "What was the name of Beyoncé's solo debut album?",
    optA:"I AM ... SASHA FIERCE",
    optB:"DANGEROUSLY IN LOVE",
    optC:"SURVIVOR",
    optD:"B'DAY",
    answer: "DANGEROUSLY IN LOVE"
  },
  {
    prompt: "In what song does Beyoncé sing: 'I swore I'd never fall again, but this don't even feel like falling'?",
    optA:"BROKEN-HEARTED GIRL",
    optB:"HALO",
    optC:"CRAZY IN LOVE",
    optD:"ALL NIGHT",
    answer: "HALO"
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is the name of Beyoncé's all-female tour band?",
    optA:"SUGA MAMA",
    optB:"HEARTBREAKERS",
    optC:"SWEET THINGS",
    optD:"PARLIAMENT FUNKADELIC",
    answer: "SUGA MAMA"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who did Beyoncé marry in 2008?",
    optA:"KANYE WEST",
    optB:"SEAN COMBS",
    optC:"JAY-Z",
    optD:"ICE CUBE",
    answer: "JAY-Z"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Destiny's Child released their major label debut song on the soundtrack of what film?",
    optA:"I, ROBOT",
    optB:"ENEMY OF THE STATE",
    optC:"BAD BOYS",
    optD:"MEN IN BLACK",
    answer: "MEN IN BLACK"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who did Beyoncé portray in the movie Cadillac Records?",
    optA:"BILLIE HOLIDAY",
    optB:"ARETHA FRANKLIN",
    optC:"ELLA FITZGERALD",
    optD:"ETTA JAMES",
    answer: "ETTA JAMES"
  },
  {
    prompt: "What perfume did Beyoncé develop with Tommy Hilfiger?",
    optA:"DREAMGIRL",
    optB:"TRUTH OR DARE",
    optC:"TRUE STAR",
    optD:"ENCHANTED",
    answer: "TRUE STAR"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who was 'Pretty Hurts' originally written for?",
    optA:"KATY PERRY",
    optB:"TAYLOR SWIFT",
    optC:"JAY-Z",
    optD:"RIHANNA",
    answer: "KATY PERRY"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who does Beyoncé dance with in the music video for 'Naughty Girl'?",
    optA:"KANYE WEST",
    optB:"USHER",
    optC:"MICHAEL EALY",
    optD:"JAY-Z",
    answer: "USHER"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which track earned Beyoncé Song of the Year at the 2010 Grammy Awards?",
    optA:"BROKEN-HEARTED GIRL",
    optB:"DIVA",
    optC:"IF I WERE A BOY",
    optD:"SINGLE LADIES (PUT A RING ON IT)",
    answer: "SINGLE LADIES (PUT A RING ON IT)"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which music video features Jay Z as a passenger in a car speeding along Mission Road in Los Angeles, where he encounters Beyoncé, standing in the middle of the road?",
    optA:"ME, MYSELF AND I",
    optB:"NAUGHTY GIRL",
    optC:"CRAZY IN LOVE",
    optD:"BABY BOY",
    answer: "CRAZY IN LOVE"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Destiny's Child got their name from what book of the Bible?",
    optA:"ISAIAH",
    optB:"EXODUS",
    optC:"REVELATIONS",
    optD:"PSALMS",
    answer: "ISAIAH"
  },
  {
    prompt: "How many Grammy Awards did Beyoncé earn for her third solo album?",
    optA:"FOUR",
    optB:"TWO",
    optC:"SIX",
    optD:"ZERO",
    answer: "SIX"
  },
  {
    prompt: "As a seven-year-old, Beyoncé won a talent show singing what Beatles song?",
    optA:"LET IT BE",
    optB:"YESTERDAY",
    optC:"YELLOW SUBMARINE",
    optD:"IMAGINE",
    answer: "IMAGINE"
  },
  {
    prompt: "What was the original name of Destiny's Child?",
    optA:"PATRON SAINTS",
    optB:"702",
    optC:"GIRL'S TYME",
    optD:"BLAQUE",
    answer: "GIRL'S TYME"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Beyoncé's younger sister was a back up dancer for what group?",
    optA:"'N SYNC",
    optB:"DESTINY'S CHILD",
    optC:"TLC",
    optD:"JONAS BROTHERS",
    answer: "DESTINY'S CHILD"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Where was Beyoncé born?",
    optA:"AUSTIN",
    optB:"SAN ANTONIO",
    optC:"HOUSTON",
    optD:"DALLAS",
    answer: "HOUSTON"
  },
  {
    prompt: "What is the name of Beyoncé's fashion line?",
    optA:"BEY HIVE",
    optB:"TIDAL",
    optC:"PAPER CROWN",
    optD:"HOUSE OF DEREON",
    answer: "HOUSE OF DEREON"
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who was the manager of Destiny's Child?",
    optA:"BEYONCE'S MOTHER",
    optB:"BEYONCE'S BROTHER",
    optC:"BEYONCE'S FATHER",
    optD:"BEYONCE",
    answer: "BEYONCE'S FATHER"
  },
  {
    prompt: "In what song does Beyoncé sing: 'What you wear is all that matters'?",
    optA:"***FLAWLESS",
    optB:"PRETTY HURTS",
    optC:"UPGRADE U",
    optD:"RUN THE WORLD",
    answer: "PRETTY HURTS"
  },
  {
    prompt: "What was the name of Beyoncé's second solo album?",
    optA:"B** DAY",
    optB:"B-DAY",
    optC:"B'DAY",
    optD:"B_DAY",
    answer: "B'DAY"
},
];
